That bastard!
Claire wanted to scream.
Marty honey, dinner.
I'm sick
of this crap.
His legs?
That seemed to piss her off.
And he ate me out
for an hour.
Lisa, you know,
it's all about attitude.
If you want it, you can get it.
You just got to get
your fuckin' ass on the beach.
- Work for it.
- Whatever.
Excuse me,
sandwich boy?
Aren't you supposed
to wear gloves,
'cause I don't know
where those hands have been.
Fuckin' pigs, man!
- My name's Marty, what's yours?
- Just give me the sub, asshole.
Ask the bitches to meet us,
fuckhole! We'll party.
We're going surfing, at 3:00.
If you want to meet us
at North Beach.
Maybe we'll think about it.
Great, babe,
you can be my date.
My friend here
will take that one.
Hey, fuck you, man.
- Those guys were fine.
- He was making fun of me.
No shit. He was just being
an asshole. Guys are like that.
But the other one,
the shorter one--
- The cute one.
- Yeah, Marty.
He acted like
he wanted to meet you.
- Meet you, you mean.
- No, his buddy's got dibs on me.
His buddy's the boss.
I've never been
around such a hunk.
Oh!
- Cute butt.
- Yeah.
He's sweet.
The other one's an asshole.
You wanna go to a party?
Sure.
- You're a pretty hot surfer.
- Thanks.
You could go pro.
What planet
are you living on?
Earth, fucker!
Compared to you,
he's fuckin' Kobe Bryant.
- What do you guys want?
- Go get a bottle of tequila.
Can you give me some money?
I only got six bucks.
What was that, boy?
Was it "Yes sir, boss. I'll buy
that booze for you now?"
What I thought, bitch!
You're an asshole.
Baby,
you know what I like.
Come on up here.
I'm starting to dig you a little bit.
Damn, baby.
- Welcome to the party, bitch!
- Fuck!
Take your pants off.
Come on, baby.
You're fuckin' beautiful.
Back up.
Yeah.
Good morning.
- I got a new boyfriend, Ma.
- A new what?
- A new boyfriend.
- A boyfriend?
What kind?
A hunk.
Really?
Yeah,
you're gonna meet him.
I hear your cute friend
gives good phone.
Marty's the best.
He'll make you come in two minutes.
- Can I call him?
- No, he'll call you.
He lives with
his parents, you know.
Okay look,
right now...
$100 if he gets
on stage and dances.
I hope you know
you're getting up there.
No way, man.
No way.
Come on. A hundred bucks
is a hundred bucks.
I can make the money
somewhere else.
Get the fuck up there
right now, it's $100.
Go!
Get up there.
Make 'em proud.
160, 180, 200...
Plus what you got,
that's 300.
What's the matter, man?
You enjoyed that,
back there, didn't you?
Hell no. I ain't queer
like those guys.
Bullshit.
can you shut the f**k up
You're such an a**hole
Fuck you!
- Look out!
- Man!
You fuck, you fucked up
my fuckin' car!
- I'm sorry.
- Fuck!
Watch the fuck out!
You're gonna make me wreck!
- You stupid fuck!
- Oh, fuck!
- You piece of shit!
- Motherfucker!
- Fuck this goddamn shit!
Marty?
Hey, get in the car.
Fuck you, man.
I'm sorry, man.
Let's just go.
Let's go, I'm sorry.
Get your fuckin' hands
off me, Bobby.
I'm really sorry.